bnmla.com 2014-07-10

# Privacy Policy | engage:BDR

Updated as of February 10, 2014

INTRODUCTION

At Engage BDR, privacy is a top priority and we provide this Privacy Policy to outline our practices and procedures with respect to information collection and use to enable you to make an informed decision about sharing information with us when you use our website. Engage BDR is an advertising network which means we may deliver advertisements to the websites you visit. 

After reviewing the Privacy Policy, if you have any further questions, please contact us at: privacy@engagebdr.com  
ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS

Engage BDR strongly recommends you read this Privacy Policy carefully. This is our official Privacy Policy which forms part of your legal agreement with us under our Terms and Conditions . By visiting this website (“Website”) and/or sharing information with us, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy and any Terms and Conditions posted on our Website or otherwise linked to herein. 

WE CAN MODIFY THIS PRIVACY POLICY

This page was last updated as of the date at the top of this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to modify, add or delete provisions of this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time, and we will post a notice and the effective date of any change on our Website. If you have given us your email address to use or we have some other means of contacting you, we may also do so in any or all of those ways, but our posting is the only official and required notice you will receive. Your use of our Website after the effective date of any such modification means you accept and agree to be bound by the Privacy Policy, as modified. We urge you to come back to this web page and review this Privacy Policy regularly so that you remain aware of the terms and conditions that apply to you.

INFORMATION ENGAGE BDR COLLECTS

_Personal Identifiable Information_

Personal Identifiable Information (PII) is data that can be used directly, or with reasonable effort, indirectly, to contact or identify you, and may include, but is not limited to, your name, phone number, date of birth, age, gender, email address and home address, among other things. 

Engage BDR does not intentionally collect PII from Website visitors and takes precautions to avoid the collection of PII. Engage BDR cannot guarantee it may not inadvertently come into the possession of PII. Additionally, Engage BDR may obtain PII from our Website when you, the Website user, choose to provide it to Engage BDR. Collection of PII may occur when you send us PII about yourself in an email or by completing an online form or registration on our Website. PII obtained in this manner may be stored for a reasonable time for record keeping purposes. You are not required to provide any PII to us unless you choose to access features on this site which require the information. If you do not agree with the terms of this policy or other terms of use on this website, then you should immediately exit this website and discontinue using the site.

_Non-Personal Identifiable Information (Non-PII)_

Non-PII is information that cannot be used to personally identify the user. As part of our on-going efforts to ensure the best possible experience for all recipients of Engage BDR advertising, we may use log files, web beacons and cookies to collect data from browsers, advertiser and third party sites to aggregate information. The information collected is used for marketing purposes, enabling us to determine which advertisements perform well, allows us to more effectively match advertisements and website content to your interests, assists us in improving the operation of our services, helps us to maintain the quality of our services, enhances our services to our business partners and clients and enables us to provide general statistics to our business partners and clients regarding use of Engage BDR’s services. 

HOW INFORMATION IS COLLECTED

“Log files” track actions occurring on Sites and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, click data and types of advertisements viewed.  
“Web beacons” consist of small strings of code that represent a graphic image request on a web page, a page in an online application, or in an email. A graphic image can be associated with the web beacon, but it is not required. When an image is present, usually the image is designed to blend into the background of the web page, application, or email in which it appears. Often a beacon will be placed by an online data collecting company without an image, so it is invisible to the user, and in the smallest discrete space possible on the screen. This is a “pixel” and is essentially an invisible web beacon. Pixels and web beacons can be used for site traffic reporting, unique visitor counts, advertising auditing and reporting, personalization, and other uses. They do this typically by writing or editing cookies on each user’s computer. Therefore, like cookies, they cannot be used to log keystrokes, copy personal files from your computer, or replicate like a virus. 

“Cookies” are files (e.g. HTTP cookies) that are stored on your Internet enabled device (which includes your computer, BlackBerry or other PDA). Cookies are used to improve the experience web users have when they see web advertisements and ensure that when a web user clicks on an advertisement, they are sent to the correct click-through destination. We may use Cookies to estimate the total reach of an advertising campaign, as well as frequency of display. This allows advertisers to determine with greater accuracy the composition of the audience they reach. Cookies are also used to control the delivery of a series of advertisements to a web browser, and to limit the number of times a web browser receives any one advertisement. You can turn off all cookies, in case you prefer not to receive them. You can also have your computer warn you whenever cookies are being used. For both options you have to adjust your browser settings (such as Mozilla, Firefox, or Internet Explorer). There are also software products available that can manage cookies for you. Please be aware, however, that when you choose to reject cookies, this choice may limit the functionality of the website you visit and you may lose access to some of its features.

HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

We will only use information we collect or obtain when you use our Website, as described in this Privacy Policy, for our internal purposes or to ensure compliance with our Terms and Conditions. It any time in the future, we decide we are going to use your information in a way that differs from our then current Privacy Policy, we will give you notice as described in the section above entitled WE CAN MODIFY THIS PRIVACY POLICY, at least 30 days’ in advance notice.

SHARING YOUR INFORMATION  
We do not share any information except as provided elsewhere in this Privacy Policy.

SECURITY

Information that Engage BDR collects is stored on servers that are managed using standard security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information in an effort to protect information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure. Please keep in mind, however, that whenever you give out PII online there is a risk that third parties may intercept and use that information. While Engage BDR strives to protect your PII and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online. By using this site, you expressly acknowledge and agree that we do not guarantee the security of any data provided to or received by us through this site and that any PII, other data or information received from you through the site is provided to us at your own risk, which you expressly assume. 

DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES 

Engage BDR may disclose your information to third parties when we reasonably believe we are obligated to do so by law, and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual prohibited activities, including but not limited to, fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person. Release of your personal data for security purposes, as described in this Privacy Policy to any person or entity under any circumstances shall be based on a determination made solely by us, exercising our own discretion, permission for which is expressly granted by you to us in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  
Engage BDR may share Non-PII and PII with entities controlling, controlled by, or under common control with Engage BDR. Engage BDR may transfer information, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets, bankruptcy, or other corporate change.

RETENTION OF INFORMATION

We retain Non-PII to more effectively match advertisements and website content to your interests for no more than eighteen (18) months. Aggregate reports generated from such data may be retained for a longer period.

DISCLAIMERS

The Privacy Policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond Engage BDR’s control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation. This online privacy policy only applies to information collected through this site. This privacy policy does not apply to any information we may collect from you in any place other than this website.

Engage BDR may provide links to third party websites from our Website. Third party websites may utilize a variety of data collection tools to collect visitor data. Engage BDR is not responsible for the privacy practices, policies or content of third party websites. Please review the privacy policy of individual websites visited to learn more about the collection practices of that website. Even if we have a relationship with a third party you may encounter or see on our Website, the advertising, links or references to third parties or any of their websites, including any cookies or other technology they may use, are not under our control and they have their own terms, conditions, policies and practices that apply to you in connection with their websites, including those concerning collection, use and disclosure of your information.

OPTING OUT

You can opt out of having Engage BDR collect your Non-PII. Engage BDR offers an “opt-out Cookie” to block the placement of future Engage BDR Cookies on your system for 10 years from the time you opted out. If you have multiple internet browsers or users on the same computer, you will need to perform the opt-out operation for each browser and/or user. If you or your privacy software deletes the opt-out Cookie from your computer, you will need to repeat the process.

Please note that the above link for an opt-out Cookie is only applicable to the Engage BDR company website. Also, please note that use of the opt-out Cookie will affect our ability to provide you content and advertisements that will more effectively match your interests and may prevent us from controlling the frequency with which you may view any particular advertisement. Please report any problems related to the opt-out process to privacy@engagebdr.com.  
If you register on or with our Website, you are agreeing and consenting to receive information and updates about your use of our Website or our services for which you register. You may opt out of receiving any or all of these communications by sending an email to unsubscribe@engagebdr.com or by following the unsubscribe instructions we will include in each email we send you. 

CHANGING OR DELETING YOUR INFORMATION

We will provide you with a mechanism to allow and enable you to correct or update the PII in our current records that we have obtained from you. You can always review and change your PII by contacting us by email at privacy@engagebdr.com. Certain PII may not be changed without authentication (e.g., birth date) and you may be asked to provide additional information to allow us to confirm your identity in order to change those. If you ask us to remove your PII, we still reserve the right to retain as much of your PII and for so long as necessary to comply with our legal, regulatory, internal audit and record-keeping requirements.

CHILDREN’S PRIVACY.

Engage BDR is very sensitive to the issue of the privacy rights or children. Engage BDR Websites and services generally are neither developed for, nor directed at, children. If we are made aware that we have received information from children under the age of 13, in the absence of verifiable parental consent, we will us remove that information from our records. 

YOUR REPRESENTATIONS

YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT ANY DISPUTE OVER PRIVACY IS SUBJECT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND APPLICABLE SITE TERMS AND CONDITIONS. You also agree that you have provided notice to, and obtained consent from, any third party individuals whose information you supply to us with regard to: (a) the purposes for which such third party’s information has been collected; (b) the intended recipients or categories of recipients of the third party’s Information; (c) which of the third party’s data are obligatory and which data, if any, are voluntary; and (d) how the third party can access and, if necessary, rectify the data held about them. It is the express wish of the parties that the Privacy Policy and all related documents have been drawn up in the English language and that the English version of this Privacy Policy shall be the sole version used in interpreting and enforcing this Privacy Policy.
